manulife online how to set up your
account in manulife online and if you're
new to this channel and you want more
helpful videos like this please click
the subscribe button if you have policy
or plan with manual life it's better to
have this account in their manual life
online it's a way to pay your premiums
online and also other features that you
can access like view and download the
receipts to check your font value and a
lot here so let's proceed and create an
account so you should receive an email
the email that i received looks like
this they have a link down here if i'm
going to click this i will be redirected
to this site that's
online.manuallife.com.ph.logme
and then what i'll do is i'll click this
register now button and provide
informations that are needed here so
i'll just complete this form
then after completing the form check
this i agree to use search terms and
conditions and privacy policy before
proceeding you can
click this and read this to document
so here are those and then for me i'm
going to go ahead and click continue
and we have two options for otp or one
time password either via email or via
phone number so i'm gonna click or
choose the phone number option and click
send otp
i just receive the code and enter the
code here
and click proceed
so my id moving forward for manulife id
is the email address i just provided or
entered earlier so i'm going to set the
password now
we have an option to check your password
by clicking this eye icon
and click continue for the password i
just entered combination of alphanumeric
characters with symbols and uppercase
and lowercase letters so there we have
it i already have my account with
manulife online i have my policy here
and also my premium amount that i need
to pay and this is the due date so on
the left hand side you can check the
portfolio like the policies
documents
i'm gonna pull it up here and then for
the
claim i also have an option to do that
here
so i will not do that for now and then
oops
and there are other options here by the
way
let's see for other
menu
we have the payment here this is what i
want to do next like paying my premiums
online and then of course i can check my
profile and for other help i can do that
here like they have these faq sections
as well
so there you have it you can create your
manulife online account
and explore the options that we have in
here and take advantage of our results
that can be done online and if you find
this video helpful please click the like
button and if you think of other
tutorials or topics that we can share
online please let us know by providing a
comment below and this is lou from
invest library see you on next videos
bye